A Guide to the Susan B. Pendleton Papers 1969.0002
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
Susan B. Pendleton Papers
undated, 1926-1969
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
1969.0002
0.4 Linear Feet
Poetess from Hebron, Connecticut.
Biography
Poetess of Hebron, Connecticut.
Scope and Content
The collection contains letters written to Charles Coleman Sellers of Ardmore, Pennsylvania from Susan B. Pendleton of Hebron, Connecticut. Some of the letters are also addressed to Helen, presumably Mrs. Charles Sellers. The poems in folder 10 were all included in correspondence sent to Mrs. Catherine Maybury Seelye of the Acquisitions Department in Wilbur Cross Library, University of Connecticut.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in one series.
Series I: Papers (undated, 1926-1969)
Restrictions on Access
The collection is open and available for research.
Acquisition Information
Portions of the collection were acquired from Ms. Pendleton in 1969.
Publications (documents); Correspondence; Hebron (inhabited place); Periodicals; Twentieth century.; Literature; Contemporary verse. (periodical); Connecticut (state); American poetry; Poetry; Poets; Photographs; Sellers, Charles Coleman, 1903-1980; Dow, Lorenzo, 1777-1834.
- Series I: Papers, undated, 1926-1969
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1928 January - June (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1928 July - December (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Photograph, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Poems, circa 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Poems and lyrics, undated, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 11)